When you're building data visualizations for explanatory purposes, focus on simplicity.
عند إنشاء عروض البيانات لأغراض توضيحية، يُرجى التركيز على مدى بساطتها.
We can make good visuals by avoiding making bad visuals.
يمكننا إنشاء عناصر مرئية جيدة بتجنب العناصر المرئية السيئة.
And that might seem like silly advice,
وقد تبدو نصيحة سخيفة،
but the key to good visualizations is considering your data-ink ratio,
لكن السبب الرئيسي للحصول على مرئيات الجيدة هو مراعاة نسبة الحبر المستخدم لعرض البيانات،
your visual encodings, and keeping the data integrity.
والترميزات المرئية، والحفاظ على سلامة البيانات.
Further advice is to focus your audience attention on the purpose of your visualization.
وتتمثل بعض النصائح الأخرى في تركيز انتباه المشاهد على الهدف من المرئيات.
If the insight isn't easily apparent,
إذا لم تكن الفكرة واضحة،
then your visualization is probably too complicated.
فمن المحتمل أن تكون المرئيات أكثر تعقيدًا.
Remove the extras and focus on conveying your message.
تخلصوا من العناصر الإضافية وركِّزوا على نقل رسالتكم.
Only use color where necessary.
لا تستخدموا الألوان إلا عند الضرورة فقط.
If there isn't additional information being
إذا لم تكن هناك معلومات إضافية
gained by the audience member from the use of color,
يتم اكتسابها من أحد المشاهدين من استخدام اللون،
this is an indication you probably don't need it.
فهذه إشارة قد لا تحتاج إليها على الأرجح.
A reminder that the design techniques in this lesson are focused on explanatory visuals.
وكتذكير، إن تقنيات التصميم في هذا الدرس تركز على المواد المرئية التوضيحية.
In the upcoming lessons,
في الدروس القادمة،
you will learn to build data visualizations in Tableau.
ستتعلمون كيفية إنشاء مؤثرات عرض البيانات في Tableau.
Often, these visuals are created with a tool for exploratory purposes.
غالبًا ما يتم إنشاء هذه العناصر المرئية باستخدام أداة لأغراض استكشافية.
For final analysis, you should consider moving the insight of
في التحليل النهائي، يجب أن تفكروا في نقل فكرة
this tool to your audience using something with less distractions.
هذه الأداة إلى جمهوركم باستخدام طريقة أقل تشتيتًا.
These tools often have a lot going on and the extras can distract from your insight.
غالبًا ما تحتوي هذه الأدوات على الكثير ويمكن أن تشتت العناصر الإضافية أفكاركم.
This is a beautiful dashboard.
هذه لوحة معلومات رائعة.
But if you are trying to highlight a particular insight from it,
ولكن إذا كنتم تحاولون تسليط الضوء على فكرة معينة منها،
I'm distracted by all the colors.
فإنني مشتت من جميع هذه الألوان.
The fact that there are so many different parts is overwhelming.
حقيقة أن هناك العديد من الأجزاء المختلفة بالغة بعض الشيء.
And since I'm not familiar with the data,
وبما أنني لست على دراية بالبيانات،
I don't even know where to start with what question is being answered.
فإنني لا أعرف حتى من أين أبدأ السؤال الذي تتم الإجابة عنه.
This leads nicely into the final points of this lesson. Data storytelling.
يوضح ذلك النقاط النهائية في هذا الدرس جيدًا. السرد القصصي للبيانات.